Are you really dating Reo?
What?
You two went on a date?!
Please explain this.
Actually, we're...
You should just tell them.
You two went on a date.
Yeah. It was a punishment date.
- A punishment date?
- That's right.
They were playing a game with me and Kitauchi.
Reo and Kasumi lost,
so we thought up a funny punishment.
And that's how they end up going on a date.
That makes sense. I knew it couldn't be real.
- Right? I thought it was totally impossible!
- Absolutely!
No way, you guys totally believed it!
No way!
Better to keep it quiet, right?
It's pretty embarrassing.
There's no way I'd date someone with so little sex appeal.
Be grateful I went on a date with you, even if it was a punishment.
Let's practice.
[Ai-Chan's Secret | Episode 10]
Takumi!
You surprised me! What's up?
Thanks for covering for me.
It seemed like Reo wanted it to come out, though.
Well...
But...
Reo says he'll wait for me to feel ready.
And will he be so soft on you forever?
You prioritize your own feelings over his, don't you?
Which means he's still not number one to you.
Of course he's number one!
Ai, what's wrong?
I think...
I've been putting myself first in everything.
I don't have the courage or confidence
to say I'm Reo's girlfriend.
I'm jealous.
Jealous?
Of what?
No matter what, Reo thinks of you and stands by you.
And even though you have doubts, you always do your best to think of Reo, too.
I think that's wonderful.
You're not alone, Ai.
Reo accepts every part of you.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
It was terrible of me to go along with Takumi's lie.
I'm sorry, too.
I tried to do the thing you wanted least in the world.
No...
I'm not perfect, either.
Even though I know how you feel, I got jealous of Takumi
and made you worried about Yuka.
We'll face more challenges in the future,
but we can overcome them together, right?
Right.
[Maid Cafe | Spica]
What was that about today?
- I was just trying to help.
- Who told you to do that?
What were you going to say, then?
Kasumi didn't seem ready for that.
You act like you're helping, but what are you planning?
Nothing. Her meddling has just changed.
I guess... It's her last gamble.
Christmas Eve, huh?
But we have an exam before then, don't we?
Oh, crap! I totally forgot about that.
So I told Dad I wanted him to let us to stay in Japan...
but he said no.
There's nothing we can do.
Are you really okay leaving things with Ai like this?
We won't be in Japan come the new year!
I want to give it everything I've got one final time.
I don't want to be apart from Reo.
I don't want to transfer schools.
[Kafuu High]
Morikawa? You don't have cleaning duty, right?
It won't hurt, will it? Working together.
Thank you.
My blackboard eraser seems to like you, too.
What are you talking about?
Those two didn't tell us they were changing schools.
We've been through a lot, but we all became friends, huh?
Kasumi?
Do you have a second?
Oh? Where is Aiko?
Well...
Reo, there's something I want to talk to you about.
Sorry, I'm in a bit of a rush.
If you go on dates as punishment,
please go on one with me too!
What are you talking about?
I'm transferring schools.
Takumi is too.
Reo...
I like you.
I really like you.
At first,
I just wanted your attention and dug my heels in.
But...
at some point,
my feelings became real.
I couldn't do anything to stop it.
So this is my final request.
I love looking at the sky like this by myself.
But you're here with me today.
Morikawa...
Kiss me.
- I'm sorry.
- Don't tell me you're sorry.
Just say my name...
and hold me one last time.
Ikumi...
Thank you.
Look at that!
Oh! Mt. Fuji is so beautiful!
I really
do like you.
You would let me kiss you?
This isn't like you at all.
You heard, didn't you?
That we're changing schools.
Were you trying to help me make one final memory?
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to do that.
Why are you making her cry?
He didn't! It's my fault!
Reo… I'm sorry.
That's enough. Let's go.
I want to tell everyone that you're mine,
Aiko...
That I'm the only one who can touch you.
Reo...
Aiko...
Don't let go of my hand.
I'm home.
Oh, Aiko! Your friend stopped by.
Ranji took her up to your room.
Hiroko?
Ikumi?
You're really Mai, aren't you?
Yeah...
Was it fun for you to lie and trick me?
The person Reo cherished was someone like you.
I'm disappointed.
I want my tears back.
I feel bad about this.
Why would you do something like this?
Do you not have any confidence or something?
If you have no self-confidence,
you're denying the feelings of those who say they love you.
I'm not like Takumi.
If you're not going to do it, I'll tell everyone about this myself!
Are you okay?
I'm sorry about yesterday.
I took advantage of your kind heart.
I do like you, Takumi.
But...
it's different than how I like Reo.
I know.
On the roof,
I wasn't trying to help you make memories.
I was just sad.
Because you and Ikumi...
are my precious friends.
That's more like the Kasumi I love.
♫ What awaits in this battle of love? ♫
♫ It seems it won't end in a draw ♫
♫ You hated loosing, ♫
♫ So I won't let you go easy on me ♫
[Aiko Kasumi]
If you have no self-confidence...
you're denying the feelings of those who say they love you.
I want to openly date you as "Aiko".
And that's what I can't stand. It's too embarrassing. How could I tell everyone?
Aiko, let's keep this all a secret, until you're ready to tell everyone...
that you're "Mai".
This is Kasu—
Mai Toda. She is my girlfriend.
I don't like you because you're Mai.
The one I like is Aiko Kasumi.
I want to tell everyone that you're mine,
♫Like a wave coming back.♫
Aiko...
♫ I'll steal you away before anyone gets the chance ♫
♫ Lips to exchange ♫
Exams are over.
What are you going to do for Christmas?
I...
- want to put an end to this secret.
- Huh?
At first, I became Mai on a whim,
but, before I knew it, I started to have fun when I was Mai.
But
I don't want to hide...
my feelings for you anymore.
I don't think I'm worthy of being your girlfriend.
Everyone might make fun of me.
I didn't have any confidence.
But... you've given me
so much confidence, Reo.
I don't want to hurt you anymore.
So... I'll tell everyone.
I'll quit Spica,
and I'll openly
date you, Reo.
Really?
Are you sure?
Yeah.
The number one person to me
is you, Reo.
Merry Christmas!
[Maid Cafe | Spica]
- Here you are.
- No way! Thanks!
Spica's special dish… mini hamburgers.
Merry Christmas!
Cheers!
So yummy!
- And Santa's here!
- In the flesh!
Sorry about this. Borrowing Aiko on Christmas Eve.
You don't feel bad at all, do you?
But you know, she looks like she's having fun.
Eat up! There you go.
She does.
But you've got a good eye!
You really drew out Aiko's inner traits.
Girls can look different with makeup and clothes,
but Ai has overcome a lot and has really changed.
It's all thanks to you, Reo.
- Order up.
- Got it!
Looks good!
I hope we can always keep playing games together!
Oh! Thank you, Master!
- Merry Christmas!
I'll keep coming next year to see you.
- Absolutely, I will!
- That's great!
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
- Take a look!
- Oh? I can open it?
Here you are!
It looks so good!
Here you go, Master.
- Kasumi is not here yet?
- No, not yet.
Someone text her.
Do you know it?
I don't.
You go ahead.
Excuse me!
Everyone, please listen.
Actually...
Aiko Kasumi is...
Oh! Aiko said her stomach hurts, and she's not coming!
What?
Now we'll have Kenji's Magic Show!
- No way!
- Awesome!
- Kenji! Kenji!
- For real?
Kenji! Kenji! Kenji!
Okay, okay, I'll do it!
All right! Here I go.
You don't have to tell everyone.
- What are you talking about?
- Things are fine as they are.
Those feelings make me more than happy enough.
But that's—
I'm the only one who can know everything about you.
Is it a good thing
to continue the secret?
It doesn't matter
if it's good or bad.
What matters more than anything is you smiling.
Thank you to the entire Love Under Disguise 💕 Team
Thank you to the Channel Manager, geseende
Thank you to the Chief English Editor: Cerejacult
Thank you to the Japanese-English subtitler: nerdishh
Thank you to all Moderators
You're not going to expose her secret?
Reo doesn't want it exposed, so my hands are tied.
We were totally rejected by those two, huh?
I should never have developed an unrequited love.
That's not true.
Kenji!
Love isn't just about being reciprocated.
You've taught me how important it is to express your feelings.
What do you mean?
Well, I guess I'm trying to say...
I like you, Ikumi.
Thank you, Kenji.
Yeah, yeah, yeah...
All right, Takumi! Let's go to a mixer or something!
It's not... This is just for Takumi!
This Rudolph only belongs to you, Hiroko!
The bingo tournament funded by Manager Rudolph's pocket money is about to begin!
♫ Just wanna, wanna, wanna, wanna go and take it ♫
O seventy!
- There it is!
- I got it!
If you hurt Reo, I'll never forgive you.
Thank you, Ikumi.
I'll miss having you guys around.
You're just saying that.
You could tell?
So rude!
♫ Lonely, lonely, lonely, lonely only ♫
♫ Lonely, lonely, lonely, lonely oh no ♫
♫ Just wanna, wanna, wanna, wanna go and take it ♫
♫ Take my heart ♫
I wonder
if they're up in the sky right now.
Things are too quiet. It's throwing me off.
It's warm.
It is.
Since I've been with you,
I've realized a lot of things.
There's lots more things I don't know,
but I want to find out
about them with you.
The good things,
the bad things...
Everything.
Are you just
ditzy?
What?
- Or are you trying to tempt me?
- Oh!
♫ What awaits in this battle of love? ♫
♫ It seems it won't end in a draw ♫
♫ You hated loosing, ♫
- You know...
- Yeah?
When we came here on our first date
I had so much fun.
Why not just say it's your first time?
My heart was racing.
♫ I want to steal you away ♫
But I thought those feelings weren't love.
♫ I make you acting like a kid with just a sweet kiss ♫
What about now?
I don't have to spell it out.
Say it.
♫ I'll let you get near just to return you like a wave ♫
I love you, Reo Amano.
I
love you.
♫ I make you acting like a kid with just a sweet kiss ♫
♫ Only I know this ♫
♫ Rather than touching, we can melt
into one another's embrace ♫
♫ I'll let you get near just to return you like a wave ♫
♫ I'll steal you away before anyone gets the chance ♫
♫ Lips to exchange ♫
[This drama is a work of fiction]